Finding Aid for American Council on Alcohol Problems Records 1883-2015
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Thirtieth National Convention Banquet, Columbus, OH December 17, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Saloon League Convention Banquet, Saint Louis December 4, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Resist Repeal, Anti Saloon League Convention Banquet, Washington DC December 12, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Conn. Delegation to the Anti-Saloon League Convention Banquet, Washington DC January 16, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Twenty Fourth National Convention Banquet, Anti Saloon League Convention Banquet, Detroit, MI January 15-19, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Final Banquet of the Crisis Convention of the Anti-Saloon League Convention Banquet, Chicago, IL November 5-9, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Twenty Fifth Anniversary Banquet, Chicago, IL February 7, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Twenty First National Convention Banquet, Workers Conference, Washington DC January 9-11, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Last Day, Sixth Convention, Washington DC December 5, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Banquet of the Anti-Saloon League Convention Banquet, Washington DC December 18, 1912 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Eighth National Convention, Washington DC December 10, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Gov. Haskell of Oklahoma signing the Billups Prohibition Enforcement Code March 24, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Old League Headquarters, Bliss Building (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Annual conventions and other gatherings, panoramic photos of delegates
    - Golden Jubilee celebration, Columbus, Ohio November 1913 (Folder 1)
    - Board of Trustees, 15th National Convention, Columbus, Ohio 1913 (Folder 1)
    - 16th National Convention, Atlantic City July 1915 (Folder 1)
    - 18th National Convention, Washington DC December 1917 (Folder 1)
    - 19th National Convention, Washington DC June 1919 (Folder 1)
    - National Convention, Washington DC December 1921, 2 images (Folder 1)
    - Thirty Year Jubilee Convention, Washington DC January 1924 (Folder 1)
    - 25th National Convention, Washington DC January 1932 (Folder 1)
  - 15th International Congress Against Alcoholism, visit of delegates to Mt. Vernon September 1920 (Folder 1)
  - Committee of One Thousand, 1 photo in 2 parts (Folder 1)
  - Committee of One Thousand, Washington DC December 1913 (Folder 1)
  - State Convention, Springfield, Ill. June 1918 (Folder 1)
  - National Conference, World Wide Prohibition, Columbus, Ohio November 1918 (Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors, Indianapolis, Ind. April 1924 (Folder 1)
  - Women's National Committee for Law Enforcement, Washington DC April 1926 (Folder 1)
  - National Women's Christian Temperance Union Youth's Roll Call December 4, 1931 (Folder 1)
    (President Herbert Hoover is part of the gathering)
- Newsletters
  - The American Issue 2015 (Box 8)
Selective Index of Correspondents
Anti-Saloon League of Michigan.
Dec. 3, 1926; Mar. 30, 1942; May 12, 1943; Nov. 12, 1943; Mar. 22, 1944
Borah, William, 1865-1940.
March 25, 1922
Cannon, James, 1864-1944.
July 8, 1936;Sept. 21, 1936; 1939-1941; 1944
Capper, Arthur, 1865-1951.
Apr. 11, 1921; Jan. 5, 1925; Aug. 28, 1935; Sept. 5, 1935; Sept. 9, 1935
Cherrington, Ernest Hurst, 1877-1950.
Mar. 2, 1928; Apr. 16, 1928; Apr. 26, 1928; Aug. 25, 1934; Oct. 18, 1934; Apr. 22, 1940
Christgau, Oscar Gottlieb
1934-1941
Couzens, James Joseph, 1872-1936.
Jan. 30, 1925; Feb. 3, 1925
Dickinson, Luren Dudley, 1859-1943.
Mar. 8, 1940; Mar. 26, 1940
Dunford, Edward Bradstreet, 1890-1966.
1924-1935; 1939-1944; 1946-1956; 1958
McBride, Francis Scott, 1872-1955.
May 20, 1929; Sept. 27, 1929; 1932-1939
Russell, Howard Hyde, 1855-1945.
Jan. 20, 1928; Dec. 16, 1942
Smoot, Reed, 1862-1941.
Mar. 25, 1927
Taft, William Howard, 1857-1930.
Dec. 20, 1926; Jan. 20, 1927
Vinson, Frederic Moore, 1890-1953.
Mar. 5, 1924; May 21, 1924
Volstead, Andrew John, 1860-1947.
June 18, 1921; June 22, 1921; Jan. 29, 1925; Apr. 2, 1927
Watson, James E, 1863-1948.
Mar. 21, 1925; Mar. 23, 1925
Wheeler, Wayne Bidwell, 1869-1927.
1917; 1919; 1921-1927